Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES VI. Regions, 1964-1980
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VI. REGIONS
  - North Atlantic Region
    - New York
      - Rules of Procedures 1979 (Box 195, Folder 27)
      - Rules of Procedures & Operating Manual 1977-81 (Box 195, Folder 28)
      - Rural Family Planning Conference, New England 1978 (Box 195, Folder 29)
      - Training Calendar 1980 (Box 195, Folder 30)
      - Training Events Calendar 1979-81 (Box 195, Folder 31)
      - Workshops
        - Planning Workshop, (Bucks County, Bristol) 1980 (Box 195, Folder 32)
        - Regional Training Workshop 1980 (Box 195, Folder 33)
        - Spring Workshop, Washington, D.C., Capitol Hilton 1980 (Box 195, Folder 34)
        - Spring Workshop, New York City, Statler-Hilton Hotel 1978-79 (Box 195, Folder 35)
        - Spring Workshop, New York City, The Roosevelt Hotel 1977-78 (Box 195, Folder 36)
        - 1977-80 (Box 195, Folder 37)
        - Technical Assistance 1978 (Box 195, Folder 38)
  - Northeast Region
    - New York
      - Abortion, General Correspondence
        - 1973 (Box 195, Folder 39)
        - 1976 (Box 195)
      - Affiliation & Financial Data
        - 1975-77 (Box 195, Folder 40-41)
        - 1964-74 (Box 195, Folder 42-46)
      - Committees
        - 1975-77 (Box 195, Folder 47-48)
        - 1970-74 (Box 195, Folder 49)
        - Medical 1975-77 (Box 195, Folder 50-51)
      - Correspondence
        - 1977-80 (Box 195, Folder 52)
        - Director 1975-76 (Box 195, Folder 53)
        - Clare Brightman, Director 1965-74 (Box 195, Folder 54-60)
      - Executive Committee Meeting 1969-70 (Box 195, Folder 61)
      - Executive Directors Council
        - 1972-74 (Box 195, Folder 62)
        - 1976 (Box 195)
      - 4-A Funds 1972 (Box 195, Folder 63)
      - Marguerite Gilpatric, Fund Raiser 1970 (Box 195, Folder 64)
      - Meeting on Family Planning Corporation for the Capital District (HEW) 1971-72 (Box 195, Folder 65)
      - Operating Manual of the N.E. Region 1973 (Box 195, Folder 66)
      - Personnel: Employment, Vacations, Leaves, Overtime, Terminations, etc.
        - 1972-73 (Box 195, Folder 67)
        - 1976-77 (Box 195)
      - Public Affairs
        - 1974 (Box 195, Folder 68)
        - 1975-77 (Box 195)
      - James F. Potter, Assistant Director of Resources 1972-74 (Box 195, Folder 69)
      - Projects 1969 (Box 195, Folder 70)
      - Publicity 1965 (Box 195, Folder 71)
      - Correspondence, Regional Chairman and/or Representative
        - 1970-72 (Box 195, Folder 72)
        - 1975-77 (Box 195)
      - Questionnaires 1971 (Box 195, Folder 73)
      - Northeast Regional Chairman/Representative's Report of PPFA Annual Meetings
        - 1974 (Box 195, Folder 74)
        - 1977 (Box 195)
      - Regional Representative/Regional Chairman Reports
        - 1970-74 (Box 195, Folder 75)
        - 1977 (Box 195)
      - Regional Representative's Report
        - Executive and Board Meeting
          - 1973-74 (Box 195, Folder 76)
          - 1975-77 (Box 195)
          - 1972 (Box 195, Folder 77)
        - PPWP Executive Committee & Regional Representative Meetings 1970-71 (Box 195, Folder 78-79)
      - Reports
        - General
          - 1967-70 (Box 195, Folder 80)
          - 1976-77 (Box 195)
        - Clara R. Brightman, Director 1965-69 (Box 195, Folder 81)
        - Members
          - 1965-71 (Box 195, Folder 82)
          - 1975-77 (Box 195)
      - Response to the Re-Organization Report from Phyl. S. Vineyard 1973 (Box 195, Folder 83)
      - Rules of Procedure for the Northeast Region
        - 1973 (Box 195, Folder 84)
        - 1975 (Box 195)
      - Technical Assistance 1968-70 (Box 195, Folder 85)
      - Workshops
        - Pregnancy Counseling Workshop 1972 (Box 195, Folder 86)
        - Community Education for Family Planning, Rensselaerville 1971 (Box 195, Folder 87)
        - Sex Education, Mass. 1971 (Box 195, Folder 88)
        - Spring Workshop
          - Boston, Mass. 1977 (Box 195, Folder 89)
          - Rochester, New York 1976 (Box 195, Folder 90)
          - White Plains, N.Y. 1975 (Box 195, Folder 91)
          - Syracuse 1974 (Box 195, Folder 92)
          - Boston, Massachusetts 1973 (Box 195, Folder 93)
        - Woodstock, Vermont 1972 (Box 195, Folder 94)
        - Buffalo 1970-71 (Box 195, Folder 95)
        - New Haven, Conn. 1969-70 (Box 195, Folder 96)
        - Uniform Accounting 1967 (Box 195, Folder 97)
        - Regional
          - 1969-74 (Box 195, Folder 98)
          - 1975-77 (Box 195)
          - 1966-68 (Box 195, Folder 99)
      - Eve R. Dryssen, Assistant Field Director, Reports 1964 (Box 195, Folder 100)
      - Elsie Jackson, Field Consultant Reports 1964 (Box 195, Folder 101)
      - J. Calvin Willis, Notheast Consultant, Reports, Correspondence, Misc. 1964-65 (Box 195, Folder 102)
      - Formerly Eastern League
        - Dr. Mabel Ingalls 1964-68 (Box 195, Folder 103)
        - Mrs. Kenneth Ziegler 1964-69 (Box 195, Folder 104)
- SERIES VII. MINUTES
  - Annual Reports
    - 1975-78 (Box 101, Folder 1-2)
    - 1954-74 (Box 101, Folder 3-11)
    - Birth Control Federation of America 1935-39 (Box 101, Folder 12-13)
    - 1961 Income, Reported by Affiliates in Omnibus and Fund Raising, Reports, Turning Point, Annual Report, 1961 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - 1962 Income, Reported by Affiliates in Omnibus and Fund Raising, Reports, Annual Report, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - 1962 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Work File 1960 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Transition 1957 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Looking Up 1958 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Breakthrough 1959 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence 1963 (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - [Was labeled: Annual Membership Meeting, Nov. 15-16, 1960. Actually contains document reading: Proceedings of the Panel Discussion on, "Education for Marriage in Your Community," May 3, 1956.] (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - Updated Reprints List and Bibliography, 1974, Guttmacher Publication List 1962-66 (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - Reprints, AFG 1968-69, [Box 101 continued in SERIES IX: GUTTMACHER; boxes 102-195 are SERIES III: PUBLICATIONS through SERIES VI: REGIONS] (Box 101, Folder 24)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Denver, Colorado 1980 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Membership Meeting, October 2, 1980, Denver, Colorado, 1980 CLOSED (Box 196, Folder 2-3)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, December 5-6, 1980, New York, New York, 1980 (Box 196, Folder 4-5)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, January 23-24, 1981, Washington, D.C., 1980 (Box 196, Folder 6-8)
  - Transcripts, Executive Committee Meeting
    - Oct. 14, 19778:00 A.M.-10:00 A.M. (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - July 22, 1977Afternoon Session (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Jan. 28, 1977 (Box 196, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts
    - International Convocation on the World Population Crisis, June 19-20, 1974, undated (Box 196, Folder 12-13)
    - Conference of Negro Physicians on PPWP 1968 (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - Margaret Sanger Centennial, Feb. 14, 1979 (Box 196, Folder 15)
  - Transcripts, National Medical Committee Meeting
    - Wednesday, January 31, 1973 (Box 196, Folder 16-18)
    - Wednesday, March 28, 1973 (Box 196, Folder 19-20)
    - Wednesday, May 30, 1973 (Box 196, Folder 21)
    - Wednesday, September 26, 1973 (Box 196, Folder 22)
    - Wednesday, November 28, 1973 (Box 196, Folder 23)
  - Reel-to-reel recordings of Board Meeting, Feb. 20, 1971 (Box 196, Folder 24)
  - List of Convention Sessions on Audio Cassettes, Annual Meeting, Oct. 22-28, 1978, San Diego, CA, 1978 (Box 196, Folder 25)
  - Annual Meeting, Cassettes, List and Record of Borrowers 1976 (Box 196, Folder 26)
  - Annual Meeting, Convention, Session on Audio Cassettes, List and Ordering Information 1978 (Box 196, Folder 27)
  - Cassettes-1976 Convention (Box 196)
  - Tapes
    - Alan F. Guttmacher, Memorial Service, April 18, 1974, Caspary Auditorium, Rockefeller University, #1-2, 1974 (Box 197)
    - Dr. AFG tape made for WFMB Station in Indianapolis, Indiana re: Population Danger, March 1966 (Box 197)
    - Dr. Stone, Sex Lecture #1 of 1, Feb. 11, 1958 (Box 197)
    - Board of Directors 1978 (Box 197)
    - Membership Meeting 1978 (Box 197)
    - Membership Meeting and Board of Directors Meeting 1978 (Box 197)
  - Microfilm
    - Planned Parenthood Transcripts, Roll #1, Board of Directors Meeting 1966-72 (Box 197)
    - Planned Parenthood, Annual Membership Meeting Minutes, May 1956-Oct. 1972 (Box 197)
    - Role No. 6, pre-1967 (Box 197)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, October 1, 1980, Denver, Colorado 1980 (Box 197, Folder 1-2)
  - Membership Meeting, 2:30 P.M., Houston, Texas 1979 (Box 197, Folder 3-4)
  - Transcripts, Annual Membership Meeting
    - Oct. 28, 19781978 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Oct. 27, 1978 1978 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - 10/15/77, 9:00 A.M. 1977 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - 10/14/77, 2:00 P.M.1977 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - 10/30/76 1976 (Box 197, Folder 9-10)
    - Oct. 19, 19741974 (Box 197, Folder 11-12)
    - October 27, 19731973 (Box 197, Folder 13-14)
  - Transcripts, Board of Directors Meetings
    - 1/26/80, San Antonio, Texas1980 (Box 198, Folder 1-2)
    - 11/16/79, 8:30 A.M., Houston, Texas 1979 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - June 1-2, 1979, New York, N.Y. 1979 (Box 198, Folder 4-5)
    - 6/1/79, Joint Session, Friday 1:45 P.M., N.Y.C. 1979 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Feb. 9-10, 1979, Washington, D.C. (Box 198, Folder 7-8)
    - October 27-28, 1978, Saturday, San Diego, California 1978 (Box 198, Folder 9-11)
    - May 30-31, 1980 1980 (Box 198, Folder 12-13)
    - June 3, 1978, New York City 1978 (Box 198, Folder 14-15)
    - October 14-15, 1977 1977 (Box 198, Folder 16-17)
    - June 3-4, 1977 1977 (Box 198, Folder 18-19)
    - Jan. 29, 1977, 8:30 A.M., Albuquerque, NM 1977 (Box 198, Folder 20)
    - Jan. 28, 1977, 2:30-6:00 P.M., Albuquerque, NM 1977 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Oct. 29-30, 1976 1976 (Box 199, Folder 2-3)
    - June 4-5, 1976 1976 (Box 199, Folder 4-5)
    - Jan. 30-31, 1976 1976 (Box 199, Folder 6-7)
    - Oct. 21-22, 1975 1975 (Box 199, Folder 8-9)
    - 5/31/75, Saturday Morning and Afternoon Sessions, 1975 (Box 199, Folder 10-11)
    - 5/30/75 1975 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - 10/18/74, 2:301974 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - June 1, 1974, Afternoon Session and Luncheon Meeting, Speaker Edward P. Morgan, 1974 (Box 199, Folder 14-15)
    - June 1-May 31, 19741974 (Box 199, Folder 16-17)
    - Feb. 23, 1974, 9:00 A.M.-5:00 P.M.1974 (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - Friday,Oct. 26, 1973, 2:00-6:00 P.M. 1973 (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - May 22-23, 19731973 (Box 200, Folder 1-3)
    - Feb. 16-17, 1973, and unedited1973 (Box 200, Folder 4-5)
  - Bylaws and Constitution, Certificate Incorporation - APPP
    - Meetings, Roosevelt Hotel, New York City 1964 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 'Past,' 1963-65 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Budget 1964-68 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - M-8725 Sobrero's Memo, re: New Affiliations of Clinicians 1964 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Publication, re: Checks from Pharmaceutical Cos. 1964-65 (Box 200, Folder 10)
  - Association of P.P. Physicians [APPP]
    - Journal, "Advances in Planned Parenthood"
      - 1971-74 (Box 200, Folder 11)
      - 1977-80 (Box 200)
    - Proposed Amendments to Constitution and Bylaws
      - 1973 (Box 200, Folder 12)
      - 1977 (Box 200)
    - Medical Dept., General Correspondence 1969-72 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Financial
      - 1972-1974 (Box 200, Folder 14)
      - 1975-80 (Box 200)
  - Medical Department, APPP
    - General, Mimeos, Memos 1970 (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Ad Hoc Committee, The Alan F. Guttmacher, M.D. Medical Lectureship
      - 1972-73 (Box 200, Folder 16)
      - 1977 (Box 200)
    - Membership Roster Index
      - 1971 (Box 200, Folder 17)
      - 1978-80, undated (Box 200)
  - APPP, Membership List 1964-68 (Box 200, Folder 18)
  - APPP
    - Medical Dept., Minutes
      - 1968-72 (Box 200, Folder 19)
      - 1978 (Box 200)
    - Nominating Committee 1965-68 (Box 200, Folder 20-21)
    - Post Graduate Day in Family Planning Services and Research, 4/5/72 (Box 200, Folder 22)
  - APPP, Postgraduate Program, Oct. 11, 1977 (Box 200, Folder 23)
  - AAPPP
    - Progress Report 1972 (Box 200, Folder 24)
    - Questionnaires, Medical Dept. 1977 (Box 200, Folder 25)
    - Reconvened Meeting, Mexico City, April 14-16, 1973 (Box 200, Folder 26)
    - Representation to Govt. Officials 1971 (Box 200, Folder 27)
    - Medical Department, Report: Future Directions of AAPPP 1972 (Box 200, Folder 28)
  - APPP, Resolutions 1973-74 (Box 200, Folder 29)
  - APPP, Annual Meeting
    - Denver, Colorado 1980 (Box 200, Folder 30)
    - Hilton Hotel, Philadelphia, PA, 10/12, 1979 (Box 200, Folder 31)
    - San Diego, CA 1978 (Box 200, Folder 32)
    - Atlanta 1977 10/12-16 (Box 200, Folder 33)
    - Papers: Abortion 1977 (Box 200, Folder 34)
    - Oct. 12-13, 1977 (Box 200, Folder 35)
    - Papers
      - Miscellaneous 1977 (Box 200, Folder 36)
      - Sterilization 1977 (Box 200, Folder 37)
  - APPP, Annual Meeting, Miami Beach, FL., 11/10-12, 1976 (Box 200, Folder 38)
  - APPP
    - 13th Annual Meeting
      - Correspondence: General, April 16-17, 1975 (Box 200, Folder 39)
      - Los Angeles, 4/17-18, Papers, 1975 (Box 200, Folder 40)
    - Annual Meeting Press Releases 1975 (Box 200, Folder 41)
    - Postgraduate Program, April 16, 1975 (Box 200, Folder 42)
    - 13th Annual Scientific Meeting, Los Angeles, California, 4/17-18/75 (Box 200, Folder 43)
    - 12th Annual Meeting, Memphis, Tenn., April 16-17, 1974
      - Correspondence (Box 200, Folder 44)
      - General (Box 200, Folder 45)
      - Papers (Box 200, Folder 46)
    - Postgraduate Program, Annual Meeting, April 15, 1974 (Box 200, Folder 47)
  - AAPPP
    - Seminar in Human Sexuality, Houston, Texas, April 11, 1973 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meetings
      - Houston, Texas, General, Mimeos, Memos 1973 (Box 201, Folder 2)
      - Detroit, Michigan, General, Mimeos, Memos 1972 (Box 201, Folder 3)
      - Kansas City, MO, Correspondence 1971 (Box 201, Folder 4)
      - Boston, Mass.
        - Correspondence 1970 (Box 201, Folder 5)
        - General, Mimeos, Etc. 1970 (Box 201, Folder 6)
        - Papers 1970 (Box 201, Folder 7)
        - Press Releases 1970 (Box 201, Folder 8)
        - Resolutions 1970 (Box 201, Folder 9)
      - San Francisco, Cal.
        - General 1969 (Box 201, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence 1969 (Box 201, Folder 11)
        - Nominating Committee 1969 (Box 201, Folder 12)
        - Press Releases 1969 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Business Meeting and President's Comments, San Antonio, Texas 1968 (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Executive Committee, San Antonio, Texas 1968 (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Annual Meeting San Antonio, Texas, Correspondence 1968 (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Letters, Dr. Denniston, San Antonio, Texas 1968 (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - Meeting, San Antonio, Texas, Miscellaneous 1968 (Box 201, Folder 18)
    - San Antonio Texas, Letters Following Meeting 1968 (Box 201, Folder 19)
    - Pierson and Langmyhr, Papers, San Antonio, Texas 1968 (Box 201, Folder 20)
    - Program Participants and Correspondence, San Antonio, Texas 1968 (Box 201, Folder 21)
    - San Antonio, Texas, Reimbursements 1968 (Box 201, Folder 22)
    - Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA., Correspondence 1967 (Box 201, Folder 23)
    - Exec. Committee, Minutes, April 2, 1967 (Box 201, Folder 24)
    - Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA., General and Mimeos 1967 (Box 201, Folder 25)
    - Proceedings of 5th, A Meeting, Atlanta, GA. 1967 (Box 201, Folder 26)
    - Atlanta Meeting Reimbursement 1967 (Box 201, Folder 27)
    - Atlanta Papers, circa 1967 (Box 201, Folder 28)
    - A Meeting, Denver, Colorado, Apr. 26-7, 1966
      - Correspondence (Box 201, Folder 29)
      - General, Mimeos 1966 (Box 201, Folder 30)
  - [OUT CARD: PP National: Physicians, Chicago Meeting, Papers 1965Complete Folder, Original Letters], [out] (Box 201, Folder 31)
  - American Association of Medical, Annual Meeting, Chicago, Ill.
    - Papers 1965 (Box 201, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence 1965 (Box 201, Folder 33)
    - General 1965 (Box 201, Folder 34)
  - AAPPP
    - Annual Meeting, Chicago, Ill.
      - Minutes 1965 (Box 201, Folder 35)
      - Dr. Perkin's Panel 1965 (Box 201, Folder 36)
  - Physicians, American Association of, A Meeting, Chicago, Ill., Releases 1965 (Box 201, Folder 37)
  - AAPPP Meeting, Chicago 1965 (Box 201, Folder 38)
  - Resolution, Gruening-Udall 1965 (Box 201, Folder 39)
  - AAPPP Meetings, Sheraton Hotel, Dallas 1964 (Box 201, Folder 40)
  - AAPPP Attendance, Dallas 1964 (Box 201, Folder 41)
  - IPPF Conferences
    - 6th International Conference
      - Correspondence
        - China Controversy 1958 (Box 201, Folder 42)
        - General 1958 (Box 201, Folder 43)
    - Lambeth Conference, London, England 1958 (Box 201, Folder 44)
    - Regional Conference, (Hague) Holland, Correspondence, General, May 1960 (Box 201, Folder 45)
    - 3rd Regional Conference (European-African Region), Warsaw, Poland, June 1962 (Box 201, Folder 46)
    - International Conferences, Meetings, Misc., General 1962 (Box 201, Folder 47)
    - 7th International Conference, Singapore, Misc. 1963 (Box 201, Folder 48)
  - "Economic Consequences of the Population Explosion," agenda 1962 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee minutes missing from microfilm 1965, 1970 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors agendas 1955-68 (incomplete) (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Annual Membership meeting, minutes table of contents 1956-72 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Panel of PPFA-WPEC 1962 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Medical Committee meeting agenda 1956-72 (incomplete) (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Affiliation Committee agendas 1958-65 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Ordering information for cassettes 1978 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm record 1956-72 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Symposia, meetings table of contents 1957-68 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Transcript, "A Forum on Man's Future," 1963 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Annual Membership meeting transcripts, table of contents 1959-71 (incomplete) (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Annual meeting transcripts 1961 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee meeting agendas 1966-70 (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Affiliation committee meeting agendas 1966-70 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors meeting, table of contents 1955-61 (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Medical Committee minutes 1963 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - Medical Committee meeting minutes, missing from microfilm 1958-59, 1965 (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, missing from microfilm 1948, 1968 (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - Indicies, Annual Membership meeting 1962-72 (Box 132, Folder 20)
  - Alan Guttmacher, IUD slides for Oliver Bird lecture 1964 (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - Alan Guttmacher Discussion, control of contraception, reel-to reel audiotape 1970 (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - Alan Guttmacher talk to students at Cornell, reel-to-reel audiotape 1970? [duplicate of 22?] (Box 132, Folder 23)
- SERIES VIII. FOREIGN
  - Proceedings of the Seventh Conference of the International Planned Parenthood Federation: Singapore, 1964
    - Papers presented 1963 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1962-63 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Western Hemisphere 4th Regional Conference, San Juan, Puerto Rico
    - Press conference 1964 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Papers and speeches 1964 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence 1963-64 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - International conferences, general correspondence 1964-65 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - 8th International Conference, Santiago Chile
    - 1966-68 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - General, miscellaneous, and speeches 1966-67 (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Conference Bandung, "Getting More Out of the Mass Media," 1969 (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - First International Medical & Scientific Congress, Sydney, Austrailia 1972 (Box 202, Folder 10)
  - Fifth All India Conference on Family Planning, report of the proceedings 1964 (Box 202, Folder 11)
  - 2nd Asian Population Conference, Tokyo 1972 (Box 202, Folder 12)
  - Foreign
    - A
      - Abortion in Foreign Countries 1952-68 (Box 202, Folder 13)
      - General, Miscellaneous 1955-69 (Box 202, Folder 14)
      - Africa
        - Correspondence 1959-70 (Box 202, Folder 15-16)
        - Liberia, Family Planning Association of Liberia 1970-71 (Box 202, Folder 17)
        - Nigeria, IUDS 1969 (Box 202, Folder 18)
      - American, Samoa (United States Unincorporated Trust Territory), Correspondence
        - 1969-74 (Box 202, Folder 19)
        - 1977 (Box 202)
      - Asia 1952-62 (Box 202, Folder 20)
      - Australia
        - 1955-72 (Box 202, Folder 21)
        - 1978-79 (Box 202)
      - Austria 1955-61 (Box 202, Folder 22)
    - B
      - Bahamas 1953-60 (Box 202, Folder 21)
      - Belgium 1955-68 (Box 202, Folder 22)
      - Bermuda 1955-73 (Box 202, Folder 23)
      - Brazil
        - General, Correspondence
          - 1963-73 (Box 202, Folder 24)
          - 1975 (Box 202)
        - 11th International Conference of Social Work 1961-62 (Box 202, Folder 25)
    - C
      - Canada
        - General, Correspondence
          - 1966-74 (Box 203, Folder 1)
          - 1975-79 (Box 203)
          - 1963-66 (Box 203, Folder 2-4)
        - The Family Planning Federation of Canada
          - 1971-74 (Box 203, Folder 5)
          - 1975 (Box 203)
        - Kitchener, Ontario, Kaufman, A.R., Parents' Information Bureau 1955-60, 1962-70 (Box 203, Folder 6)
        - Montreal
          - Family Planning Association 1964-72 (Box 203, Folder 7)
          - La Federation du Quebec pour le Planning du Naissances 1975-77 (Box 203, Folder 8)
        - Ottawa
          - Planned Parenthood Federation of Canada 1976-77 (Box 203, Folder 9)
          - PP, Correspondence 1969 (Box 203, Folder 10)
        - Toronto, PP Association
          - 1962-74 (Box 203, Folder 11)
          - 1977 (Box 203)
        - Requests for Information and Literature 1955-69 (Box 203, Folder 12)
        - Toronto, Cass Canfield, Speech, U.N. Association 1960-61 (Box 203, Folder 13)
      - Caribbean Area 1955-61 (Box 203, Folder 14)
      - Central America
        - Costa Rica 1955-66 (Box 203, Folder 15)
        - Guatemala 1955-66 (Box 203, Folder 16)
        - Honduras 1954-67 (Box 203, Folder 17)
        - San Salvador 1955-68 (Box 203, Folder 18)
      - Ceylon, Correspondence 1958-68 (Box 203, Folder 19)
      - China
        - The People's Republic of China
          - Correspondence and General 1975-77 (Box 203, Folder 20)
          - Family Planning in the People's Republic of China
            - 1971-74 (Box 203, Folder 21)
            - 1975-77 (Box 203)
          - Visit of U.S. Family Planning Delegation 1977 (Box 203, Folder 22)
          - Mrs. Vineyard's Trip 1974 (Box 203, Folder 23)
        - Taiwan
          - Correspondence and General 1969 (Box 203, Folder 24)
          - MCH Center, Demonstration Project 1968-70 (Box 203, Folder 25)
          - Correspondence 1955-68 (Box 203, Folder 26)
          - MCH Demonstration Project, Reports 1970-72 (Box 203, Folder 27)
          - T. Paul Schultz: The Effectiveness of Family Planning in Taiwan 1969 (Box 203, Folder 28)
      - Cuba 1956, 1965-68 (Box 203, Folder 29)
    - Denmark 1955-69 (Box 203, Folder 30)
    - E
      - Egypt, Correspondence 1955-66 (Box 203, Folder 31)
      - England
        - Family Planning Association 1970-73 (Box 203, Folder 32)
        - Correspondence
          - 1964-72 (Box 203, Folder 33)
          - 1977 (Box 203)
          - 1959-63 (Box 203, Folder 34)
        - Field Reports 1956 (Box 203, Folder 35)
        - Correspondence, Searle and Co., Ltd. 1963-66 (Box 203, Folder 36)
    - F
      - Far East-European Trip, Dr. R. L. Day 1965-66 (Box 203, Folder 37)
      - Far East, Vietnam, Correspondence 1969-71 (Box 203, Folder 38)
      - Fiji 1963-74 (Box 203, Folder 39)